这么说你的第一次
So your first sexual experience was
是跟女人做的咯
with a woman?
我那年15岁
All right, I was 15.
跟死党露丝在一起
It was my best friend, Ruth.
苹果酒太烈  我们醉了
And we got drunk on that hard cider.
突然之间  我们就开始亲热了
And then suddenly, I don't know, we were making out.
再说一次
Tell it again.
说真的
Seriously.
那个女人除了性爱就不会聊别的了吗
Is that woman capable of talking about anything else but sex?
不会啊  她刚才在聊地理啊
Yeah, sure. Well y'know, earlier she was talking about geography.
乔伊  她是在列举她在哪些国家做过
Joey. She was listing the countries she's done it in.
大家都获益匪浅
I think we all learned something.
各位  看我找到什么  过来看看
Hey, you guys! Look what I found! Look at this!
那是我妈的笔迹  看
That's my mom's writing. Look.
"法兰克  菲比和我  1965年毕业典礼"
"Me and Frank and Phoebe, graduation,1965."
-知道其中的含意吗  -你其实50岁了吗
- Do you know what that means? - That you're actually 50?
不不  那个菲比不是我
No, no. That's not "me" Phoebe.
是她的朋友
That's her pal, Phoebe.
从高中毕业纪念册上看来  她们是超好友
According to her high school yearbook, they were BFF.
超级好的朋友
Best Friends Forever.
-太棒了  真厉害  -是啊
- That's great!  That is so cool. - I know!
这个女人八成知道我父母所有的事情
So this woman probably could like have all kinds of stories about my parents,
甚至可能知道我爸的下落
and she might even know like where my Dad is.
我去找她的住址  她就住在海边
So I looked her up, and she lives out by the beach.
不然我们这个周末可以去海边吧
So maybe this weekend we could go to the beach?
好啊  一起去吧
Yeah! Yeah, we can!
糟糕  我去不了  我得工作
Shoot, I can't go. I have to work.
太可惜了
That's too bad.
真是扫兴
Big fat bummer.
太棒了  那我们明天开车去蒙托克
So great! Okay! Tomorrow we're gonna drive out to Montauk.
哎哟  邦妮在那里做过哦
Hey, Bonnie had sex there!
你看他们
Would you look at them?
我再也交不到男朋友了
I'm never gonna find a boyfriend again.
我会变成老姑婆
I'm gonna die an old maid.
你不会变成老姑婆
You're not gonna die an old maid.
可能会变成老处女厨娘
Maybe an old spinster cook.
-谢了  -话说  如果万不得已
- Thanks. - Besides, worse comes to worse...
我会当你的男朋友
... I'll be your boyfriend.
是啊
Yeah, right.
有什么好笑的
Why is that so funny?
你是在开玩笑吧
You made a joke, right?
所以我笑了
So I laughed.
笑得太厉害了吧
A little too hard.
怎么  我不是当男朋友的料吗
What? Am I not boyfriend material?
对啊  你是钱德勒嘛
No, you're Chandler.
你知道嘛  钱德勒
You know. Chandler!
好吧  我们刚确认了我的名字  然后打我一拳
Okay, so we've established my name, and hit me.
但假设一下  我们不是朋友
But theoretically, I mean say we weren't friends,
有人介绍我们约会  我来到你家门口
say it's a blind date. I show up at your door
然后说"嗨  很高兴认识你"
and I'm, like, "Hey,nice to meet you."
我大概会害怕用假音说话的人
I'd probably be scared of a guy using a fake voice.
真好  你买了吃的
Oh, good. You bought food.
不是  这是我的行李
No, just my luggage.
我这星期的运势很好
I am having the best karma this week.
我先是找到认识我父母的人
First I find this woman who knew my parents...
接着有个背后很多毛的客户  把海滩小屋借给我
...and then my client with the fuzzy back gives me his beach house.
你撞到快递员那件事怎么说
What about that bike messenger you hit?
我又不是在说他的运势
Oh, I wasn't talking about his karma.
看看这顶帽子
Hey, check out the hat!
慢着  我认得那顶帽子
Wait a minute, I know that hat.
我就是被那顶帽子劫持的
I was taken aboard that hat.
上面的外星人对我做实验
They did experiments on me.
害我不能生育了
I can't have children!
说真的  那帽子哪来的
Seriously, where did you get the hat?
罗斯送的
Ross gave it to me.
-我觉得她戴起来很好看  -谢谢
- I think she looks good. - Thank you.
是他买给你的
Did he buy it for you...
还是玩游戏赢的
...or win it for you?
很抱歉  时尚白痴朋友们
Excuse me, my fashion-impaired friends...
我郑重告诉你们  帽子又流行回来了
... I'm here to tell you hats are back.
这一回  小帽子都聚集成一顶超级大帽子
And this time, they've ganged up and formed one giant super-hat.
快  快  快
Go, go, go!
现在你们又觉得帽子好了吧
Now everybody wants to be under the hat!
怎么这么多沙子
What's with all this sand?
是啊  鲍伯说可能淹过水
Yeah. Bob said there might be flood damage.
不然就是他的猫很大只[得要那么多猫砂]
Either that or he has a really big cat.
没错  那是个很特别的房子
Well, yes. lt's kind of an unusual house.
有三个漂亮的卧房  没有浴室
It has three beautiful bedrooms and no baths.
但是大海就在旁边啊
But, you know, the ocean is right there.
有人在吗
Knock, knock, knock.
请等一下...请进
Hang on. Come in, come in.
好吧  你考虑完再打给我
All right, so think about it, and call me back.
-你是菲比·艾博特吗  -对
- Are you Phoebe Abbott? - Yes.
惊喜  菲比·艾博特
Surprise, Phoebe Abbott!
我是你的死党的女儿
I'm your best friend's daughter!
你是尔文的女儿吗
You're Erwin's daughter?
不  是以前的死党  你看
No. I mean your old best friend. Here.
-高中的莉莉  记得吗  -天哪  莉莉
- Lily? From high school? Remember? - Oh, God, Lily. Yes.
我当然记得莉莉了
Of course I remember Lily.
那你一定是...
Then you must be
菲比  跟你名字一样
Phoebe, Phoebe.
应该是取自你的名字
She named me after you, I guess.
看  是弗兰克
Wow. Well. Look, there's Frank!
对  没错
Yeah! Yes! Yes, yes!
那是我爸爸弗兰克
That's my dad. That's Frank!
抱歉我这么激动
I'm sorry I'm getting all flingy.
别激动  想吃饼干吗  柜台上有
Take it easy. If you want, there's cookies on the counter.
-不然喝果汁  我去调果汁汽泡酒  -不麻烦了
- Or sangria! I could make sangria! - No, no.
不用  饼干就行了  谢谢
Sorry. Cookies are good, thanks.
总之  我一直在找我爸
Anyway, I've been looking for my father.
你有他的消息  或见过他吗
Have you heard from him or seen him?
没有  对不起
Oh no, I-I'm sorry,
我高中毕业就跟大家失去联络了
I guess we lost track of everybody after high school.
好
Okay.
那就把我父母的事都告诉我  一件都不许漏
Well, so tell me everything about my parents. Everything.
我们总是形影不离
Oh, well, you know, we were always together.
老实说  其他人给我们仨取了个绰号
In fact, the other kids had a nickname for the three of us.
-是什么  什么绰号  -三贱客
- Oh, what? What was it?  - The Three Losers.
可怜的莉莉
Oh, poor Lily.
我听说她的事了
I heard what happened.
你一定非常难过
That must have been just terrible for you...
就这样失去母亲
...losing your mother that way.
不会啊  感觉很棒
Yeah, no, it was great.
知道下雨天玩什么最好吗
You know what a really good rainy-day game is?
-什么  -我是说脱衣游戏
- What? - I mean, naked game.
-脱衣扑克  我们应该来玩脱衣扑克  -不行
- Strip poker. We should totally play strip poker. - No.
你疯了吗
Are you crazy?
拜托  出门一定要玩这个
Come on. When you go away, you have to play.
这是规定
It's, like,a law.
-好了  -谢谢
- All done. - Thank you.
下一个是谁
Okay. Who's next?
不行
No way!
拜托啦  我好无聊
Come on, please. I'm bored.
你以前都让我涂过一次
You let me do it once before.
如果这是本周末的规定...
Well, if that's the rule this weekend....
-走开  -大方一点  来啦  罗斯
- Get away. - Take it like a man. Ross. Come on!
-不要  不要  -来嘛
- No, no, no! - Come on.
大坏人
Big bullies!
你们怎么样了
How are we doing?
无聊到爆
Bored and bored.
玩脱衣扑克就不会无聊
You know what? Naked card game's never boring?
不要
No!
菲比是怎么样的人
So what's Phoebe like?
我心肠好又体贴  莫妮卡呢
I'm kind, caring and sweet. What's Monica like?
我是说你去找的那个菲比
No, the other Phoebe. The one you went to see?
我觉得她知道我爸的下落
I think she knows where my dad is!
太好了
Cool!
他在哪里
Where is he?
她其实一直假装  多年没有他的消息
She was actually pretending she hasn't heard from him for years...
但是我在她冰箱上发现这张照片
...but I found this picture on her fridge.
他现在不就应该长这样吗
And look! Isn't this what he would look like now?
看着好眼熟
Totally familiar.
-对  -没错
- Oh yeah.  - Yeah.
她为什么要骗你
Why would she lie to you?
我不知道  但我们明天要吃晚饭
I don't know, but we're having dinner tomorrow.
所以我猜  也许她到时会告诉我
So I figured, she's gonna tell me then.
也许她想给他一点时间...
Maybe she just wanted to give him time...
帮我买礼物  我也不知道
...to buy me presents. I don't know.
-你们都很无聊  -是啊
- So you're all bored? - Yes.
那好吧  我闭上眼睛随便指
All right, I'm gonna close my eyes and point to someone,
被指到的人  要想一个好玩的游戏
and you, whoever I point has to come up with something fun for us to do,
大家都要照做
And we have to do it.
好  散开来  散开
Okay! Fan out! Fan out!
好
Okay.
其实我们玩这个就成
You know, we could just do this!
-好吧  我们都来玩脱衣扑克  -好耶
- Okay, umm, we all have to play strip poker. - Yes!
快乐脱衣桌游吗
Strip Happy Days Game?
我找不到扑克牌
I couldn't find any cards,
不玩这个就只能玩抽布条脱衣服了
so it was this or Strip Bag-Of-Old-Knitting-Stuff.
好
Done.
Okay.
"范佐赞给你竖起两个大拇指  你得到两分"
"Fonzie gives you two thumbs up. Collect two cool points."
莫妮卡  累积到五分
Monica, if you get five cool points,
就可以叫别人脱一件衣服
you get to make somebody take off one item of clothing.
还没人脱  但是我们都很兴奋
It hasn't happened yet, but we're all very excited.
来吧
Okay, come on.
我要替史前监识部
Daddy needs a new electromagnetic microscope
赢一台电子显微镜
for Prehistoric Forensics Department.
好的
Okay.
"带粉红托斯卡罗到机会点"
"Take Pinky Tuscadero up to Inspiration Point.
"你得到三分"  漂亮
Collect three cool points." Yeah!
现在我有五分了
Which gives me five.
我看看  脱谁衣服好呢
And let's see, who is gonna lose their clothes?
就选本游戏的发起者好了  乔伊·崔比亚尼先生
I think I pick our strip poker sponsor, Mr. Joey Tribbiani.
别激动  我就脱一只鞋子
All right, relax. It's just a shoe.
"你的乐队在阿诺德表演  你得到三分"
"Your band is playing at Arnold's. Collect three cool points."
所以我有五分  乔伊要脱四角内裤咯
Which means I have five and that means I get Joey's boxers.
好啊  合伙对付我
Fine. Gang up on me.
我会让你们脱得很难看
I got you all, right where I want you.
快脱  脱啊
Come on! Take them off!
其实有点冷
Actually, it's kind of cold.
我能不能不脱内裤
So how about I keep my boxers on,
让你们瞄一眼里面的"好货"就行了
and give you a peek at the good stuff?
我再去调些玛格丽特
All right, I'm gonna make more margaritas!
你干什么  想把我灌醉吗
What are you doing? Trying to get me drunk?
我只是调玛格丽特
I'm just making margaritas.
我去帮忙
Think I'll help her out.
这是怎么回事
What is going on here?
什么
What?
-你涂他的脚指甲  -拜托
- You're painting his toenails. - Come on.
-在屋里追着他跑  -莫妮卡  拜托
- Chasing him around the room. - Monica, please.
他也跟你打情骂俏
He's totally flirting with you too.
没错吧
He is, isn't he?
不晓得
I don't know, I don't know,
也许是因为一起来到海边  我也不知道
Maybe it's just being here at the beach together or, I don't know....
感觉上...
but it's like something
邦妮
Hi, Bonnie.
老板提早放人  我就搭火车来了
My boss let me off early, so I took the train.
你们在干什么
What are you guys doing?
玩快乐脱衣桌游
We're playing Strip Happy Days Game.
酷  算我一个
Cool! I'll catch up!
你还是觉得我...
So you still don't think I'm...
不适合当男朋友
boyfriend material?
昨晚玩游戏时  我发现你在打量我
I saw you checking me out during the game last night.
-你连裤子都没脱  -是啊
- You didn't even take off your pants. - Yes.
算你走运
Well, lucky for you.
-什么  -我胡说的
-What? - I don't know.
除了我  大家是不是都很开心啊
Well, is everybody else having just the best time?
乔伊睡觉呢
Joey's asleep.
他昏睡过去后  我们用沙子帮他保暖
After he passed out. We put sand around him to keep him warm.
我猜那对爱侣还没起床吧
Well, I assume the happy couple isn't up yet?
你们昨晚有听到吗
Did you guys hear them last night? - Yeah.
我不知道他们在干什么
I don't know what they were doing,
但有一度  真有海龟爬进屋里来
but at one point sea turtles actually came up to the house.
早安
Good morning.
-你们睡得好吗  -好极了
- Hey! How did everybody sleep? - Great.
-完全睡死过去  -我们也是
- Like a log. - Us too.
我要去散步
I'm going for a walk.
早安  胸部真不错
Good morning. Nice breasts by the way.
你怎么没来
Hey, what happened to you?
没什么  我只是想在这里看书
Oh, nothing. I just felt like hanging out and reading.
海水好舒服
The water was so great.
我们跳下桥墩  我的泳衣掉了
We jumped off this pier and my suit came off.
可惜我没看到
Sorry I missed that.
乔伊和钱德勒  肯定大饱眼福了
Joey and Chandler sure are funny.
我的头发里能积了有半个沙滩的沙子
I think I brought back half the beach in my hair.
以前光头方便多了
It was easier when I shaved my head.
我一定要告诉你
You know, I gotta tell you...
我好喜欢你光头的样子
...I just loved your look when you were bald.
真的吗
Really?
因为有时我会考虑重新剃光头
Beacuse I think about shaving it again sometimes.
-真的吗  -真的
- Really? - Yeah.
你绝对应该那样做
I mean you definitely should do that.
我是该那样做
You know what? I should do it!
谢谢你  瑞秋  你好酷
You know what? Thank you, Rachel. You are so cool.
别这么说
Oh, stop. Go on.
-去剃光头吧  -好
- Now go shave that head. - All right.
怎么了  菲比
What's the matter? Pheebs.
-跟我同名的那个菲比取消了约会  -什么
- She canceled. My namesake canceled on me. - What?
她说她突然有事得进城  她在躲我
She claims she had to go out of town suddenly. She's avoiding me.
她不想说出我爸的下落
She doesn't want to tell me where my father is.
她明知道  却不肯告诉我
She knows, and she won't tell me!
菲比  她好差劲喔
Pheebs, that sucks.
先别跟我说她差劲
Yeah, well, don't "Aww Pheebs, that sucks!" me yet.
-你要去哪里  -她出门了
- Where are you going? - Well, she's out of town
她家里一定有我爸在哪里的线索
so, there's gotta be something in her house that tellsme where my Father is.
菲比  有人称这种行为是"擅闯民宅"
Pheebs, some people call that "breaking and entering."
-这里有人这么想吗  -绝对没有
- Well, are any of those people here? - Oh no.
我会做一些好事  行吗
Look, I'll do something nice,okay?
我会把制冰盒加水  好吗
I'll-I'll fill her ice trays. Good?
大家好
Hey, everybody!
你看看你
Look what you did!
你想摸吗
You wanna touch it?
不想  但是很好看
No, but it's great.
-来嘛  摸嘛  -好吧
- Come on, touch it. - Okay.
可以摸得到每一块头骨
You can feel all the bones in your skull.
我刚和邦妮聊了一下  你猜怎样
I was having a little chat with Bonnie, and guess what?
她碰巧提到剃头这件事的幕后主使
She happened to bring up who was behind the whole head-shaving idea.
是谁呢  对  没错  就是你
And now, who was it? Oh, that's right, that's right, it was you!
是她自己想剃
That was her idea.
我只是给了她点动力
I just gave her a nudge.
她说你拿剃刀给她
She said you gave her the razor.
有人要去海里夜泳吗
So anyone up for a midnight dip in the ocean?
-我不去了  -不了  谢谢
- No, I'm good. - No ,thanks.
-好吧  待会见  -好好玩
- Okay, I'll see you in a bit. - Okay, have fun.
拜托  看起来没那么糟嘛
Come on, see? She doesn't look that bad.
你都能看到她的头反射月光
You can see the moonlight bouncing off her head!
你到底在想什么啊
What the hell were you thinking?!!
我不知道
I don't know.
你还不知道吗  你让我女朋友变成光头
You don't know?! Rach, you balded my girlfriend!
好啦  罗斯
All right. Ross.
看你跟别人在一起  难道我就好过
Do you think it's easy for me to see you with somebody else?
是你要分手的  还记得吗
Y'know, hey! You're the one who ended it, remember?
因为我很气你  不是因为我不爱你了
Because I was mad at you! Not because I stopped loving you!
-你还爱我  -不
- You still love me? - No.
你还爱我
You still love me.
是又怎样
Yeah, so?
-你也爱我啊  -不...是
- You love me. - Noo, nnnnn.
什么意思  你是不是
What does this mean?  What do you,
我是说  你想复合吗
I mean, do you want to get back together?
不是  也许吧
No! Maybe!
我不知道
I don't know.
罗斯  我还是无法原谅那你所做的一切
Ross, I still can't forgive you for what you did,
真不行  只不过有时候跟你一起
I can't, I just, but sometimes when I'm with you...
-我会觉得...  -觉得什么
- I just, I feel so... - What?
我会觉得...
I just, I feel....
-我...  -怎样
- I just - What?
我觉得...
I feel
我不管
No! I don't care!
我不要跟你练习一对一脱衣扑克
I'm not playing one-on-one strip poker with you for practice!
牌都做好了
But I made cards!
晚安
Good night.
我要上楼去了
I'm going upstairs.
-晚安  -晚安
- Good night. - Good night.
要不要练习脱衣扑克
Wanna play strip poker for practice?
我的屁股
My ass!
住手  住手  是我  是我
No! No!! It's me! It's me!
-我不想吵到你的  -那就不要闯进来
- I didn't wanna make any noise! - Then don't break in!
-对不起  -你来干什么
- I'm sorry! - What are you doing here?
我来帮制冰盒加水
I-I, came to fill your ice cube trays.
什么
What?
好吧  是这样的
Umm, okay, okay, look.
这张照片从你的冰箱上拿的
I took this picture from your fridge.
因为我认得这是我爸爸
Okay, because I know that this is my Father.
这是弗兰克·布非  你就站在他身边
Yeah, this is Frank Buffay and you are standing right there next to him.
听着  我有权利知道我的身世  好吗
Now, look I deserve to know where I came from. All right?
要是你能帮我找到爸爸  你就应该帮我
So if you can help me find my father, then you should.
否则你就是坏人
Otherwise, you're just mean.
把真相告诉我
So just tell me the truth.
好
All right.
照片上的人是查克·曼吉欧尼
The man in that picture is Chuck Mangione.
我爸是查克·曼吉欧尼吗
My father is Chuck Mangione?
不不  他跟你没有关系
No, no. That's just Chuck Mangione.
我去年卖给他一栋房子
I sold him a house last year.
非常抱歉  我真的不知道你父亲的下落
And I'm very sorry, but I really don't know where your father is.
这是实话
And that's the truth.
但是你说得对
But you're right.
人有权利知道自己的身世
I think a person should know where they come from.
所以我要说...
Which is why l....
其实...我是你的母亲
Okay...I'm your mother.
我昨天就想说  但是我...
I wanted to tell you yesterday, but I just...
我觉得很失败  然后...
...felt all floopy, and....
听我说  你们肯定要复合了
I'm telling you. You guys are totally getting back together.
才不是  她自己都搞不清楚想要什么
That's not true! She doesn't even know what she wants.
瑞秋还在气那件事
Rachel's still mad at the whole thing.
好吧  那你就后退  知道吗
Okay, then you gotta back away, all right?
你不需要受这种伤害
You don't need that kind of hurt.
听我的话  我可是...
Take it from a guy who's...
从来没跟别人长期交往过
... never had a long-term relationship.
我知道  但我真的很想上楼继续吻她
I know, but I really want to go up there and finish that kiss.
伙计们水好舒服  你们真应该去游泳
You guys, the water's great. You should really go in.
还是不了  谢谢  我刚吃了"光滑"的巧克力豆
No, thanks. I just had an M&M.
好吧  晚安
Well, good night.
晚安
Good night.
-早点回房  -没问题
- Don't be too long. - Okey-dokey.
她的头发上真是一毛不剩啊
There is not one hair on that head.
头发会长回来  好不好  而且她很风趣很酷
It'll grow back, right? And she's really fun,and she's cool.
我终于往前走了
And I'm finally moving on.
你们知道吗  要忘掉瑞秋实在...
Y'know? I mean getting over Rachel was so
我终于恢复理智  要是我上楼...
I'm finally feeling sane. And if I go up there...
吻了她...
...and I kiss her....
天哪  我好想吻她
God, I want to kiss her!
要是失败呢
And-and-and it doesn't work out, right?
我真的想再心碎一次吗
Do I wanna put myself through that again?
那我来帮你理一理
So let me get this straight.
如果你今晚选择邦妮
If you go with Bonnie,
-那是明智的决定  你可以抛开过去  -对
- you do the smart, healthy thing and move on. - Yeah.
对吧  要是选择瑞秋
Right? And if you go with Rachel,
邦妮今晚就有空了  是吗
Bonnie's free tonight?
你好
Hi there.
你的声音又怪怪的了
That's that weird voice again.
再试一次
Okay! Okay! Let me try it again,
下一个人你一定会喜欢  我发誓
You'll wanna date this next guy, I swear!
你好  我是小矮人
Hi, I'm Dorf!
你今晚的男伴
Your date for the evening.
别这样  小矮人约会耶  多有意思啊
Oh, come on. Dorf on dating? That's good stuff!